Guide to the Gospel sheet music, 1937-1970
Department of Special Collections
Gospel sheet music,
1937-1970
MISC 1058
18 pieces (1 folder)
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Contains sheet music published primarily in Chicago, Illinois from the 1930's through 1970.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None.
Acquisition Information
Purchased, 2001.
Collection Scope and Content Summary
Contains sheet music published primarily in Chicago, Illinois from the 1930's through 1970.
Access Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
African Americans--Music.; African Americans--Social life and customs.; Gospel music--United States.; Popular culture--United States.; Sheet music.
Collection Contents
- Boddie, Sylvia. Meeting tonight on the old camp ground. -- Chicaco, Ill.: Sylvia Bodie Music Studio, 1948
- Brewster, Rev. W. Herbert. Make more room for Jesus in your life / arranged by W.O. Hoyle. -- Chicago, Ill.: Bowles Music House, 1947
- Brown, Rev. W.D. and W. Morganfield. I surrender / arrangement by Kenneth Morris. -- Shreveport, LA: SU-MA Publishing Co., Inc., 1970
- Coleman, Mary Lou. When sets the evening sun / arrangements by Virginia Davies. -- Chicago, Ill.: Theodore R. Frye Publishers, 1948
- Dorsey, Thomas A. I'm just a sinner saved by grace. -- Chicago, Ill.: Thomas A. Dorsey Music Publisher, 1937
- Dorsey, Thomas A. Thank you all the days of my life. -- Chicago, Ill.: Thomas A. Dorsey Music Publisher, 1946
- George, Cassietta. Ready to serve the lord / arranged by Kenneth Morris. -- Chicago, Ill.: Martin & Morris Music, Inc., 1961, 2 copies
- Hollins, M. I come to praise him / arranged by Kenneth Morris. -- Chicago, Ill.: Martin & Morris Music, Inc., 1968
- Morris, Kenneth. He answers me. -- Chicago, Ill.: Martin & Morris Music, Inc., 1946
- Morris, Kenneth. Is it well with your soul? -- Chicago, Ill.: Martin & Morris Music, Inc., 1946
- Morris, Kenneth. Jesus is the ruler of my life. -- Chicago, Ill.: Martin & Morris Music, Inc., 1944
- Morris, Kenneth. Most of all I'm going home to see my lord. -- Chicago, Ill.: Martin & Morris Music, Inc., 1948
- Morris, Kenneth. When I join the jubilee. -- Chicago, Ill.: Martin & Morris Music, Inc., 1948
- Pace, Charles A. Hide my soul. -- Pittsburgh, Penn.: The Old Ship of Zion, 1943
- Sallie, Martin. Just a few days to labor. -- Chicago, Ill.: Martin & Morris Music, Inc., 1944